[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_05",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success_alt",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Footwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower05",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower04",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Legwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_MoiraChapman",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "amuletwindswardt3",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Handwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_response_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_06",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT2_Chestwear_15",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower06",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT2",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
		"NOTES": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_QuestReward_ArcTyp_WW_1hRshield",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 17,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_Medea03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_incomplete_new",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_response_a_new",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
		"AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
		"AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success_alt",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_title",
		"Description": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_prompt_new",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_proposal_a_new",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_FudeHinode",
		"AchievementId": "06A_B_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_title",
		"Description": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_title",
		"Description": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_IR_01_FindCreed_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_02_GetSword",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_IR_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_title",
		"Description": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_IR_02_GetSword_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_GideonStormsbane02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_IR_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_02 && 06A_MSQ_18",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_title",
		"Description": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_TalesaSerrano",
		"AchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_success",
		"ObjectiveReward": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_title",
		"Description": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_ZhangHaoyu",
		"AchievementId": "06A_TS_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_title",
		"Description": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_container",
		"AchievementId": "06A_TS_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_title",
		"Description": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_F_01_CollectJam",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_F_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_title",
		"Description": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_F_01_CollectJam_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_F_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_F_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_title",
		"Description": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_TsuiFen",
		"AchievementId": "06A_T_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_T_02_DefeatBear_title",
		"Description": "@06A_T_02_DefeatBear_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_T_02_DefeatBear_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_01_TsuiFen_b",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_T_02_DefeatBear_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_MichaelLewis03",
		"AchievementId": "06A_G_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_title",
		"Description": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_LionelDeLaRue02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_W_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_title",
		"Description": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_W_01_GetPatterns_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_Z_02 && 06A_MSQ_18",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_title",
		"Description": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_Z_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_title",
		"Description": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
		"AchievementId": "06A_S_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_title",
		"Description": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
		"AchievementId": "06A_S_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_title",
		"Description": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_response",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova01",
		"AchievementId": "06A_P_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11 && 06A_F_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_title",
		"Description": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_P_01_RecoverTools_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"Task": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_P_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_title",
		"Description": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
		"AchievementId": "06A_P_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "0",
		"Title": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_title",
		"Description": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_proposal_a",
		"InProgressResponse": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_incomplete_a",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_response_a",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup_v2",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "0699_0103_d_00_container_BarkimedesPup",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes_A2",
		"AchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "1",
		"Title": "@0699_0103_Barkimedes_title",
		"Description": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "FALSE"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_v2",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 25,
		"Task": "0699_0101_d_00_container_Barkimedes",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes_A2",
		"AchievementId": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_done",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
		"Repeatable": "TRUE",
		"Title": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_title",
		"Description": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_complete",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@0699_0101_Barkimedes_cooldown",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "FALSE",
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_v2",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 35,
		"Task": "0699_0102_d_00_container_Barkimedes2",
		"NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes_B2",
		"AchievementId": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_done",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
		"Repeatable": "TRUE",
		"Title": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_title",
		"Description": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_complete",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@0699_0102_Barkimedes2_cooldown",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "FALSE",
		"ScheduleId": "Daily"
	}
]